export const TechQuestions = [{
        prompt: "1. How many computer languages are in use?",
        optionA: "2000",
        optionB: "5000",
        optionC: "50",
        optionD: "20",
        answer: "2000",
        number: "1",
    },
    {
        prompt: "2. Which of these is not an early computer?",
        optionA: "ENIAC",
        optionB: "UNIVAC",
        optionC: "NASA",
        optionD: "SAGE",
        answer: "NASA",
        number: "2",
    },
    {
        prompt: "3.Who founded Apple Computer?",
        optionA: "Stephen Fry",
        optionB: "Bill Gates",
        optionC: "Steve Jobs",
        optionD: "Stephen Hawking",
        answer: "Steve Jobs",
        number: "3",
    },
    {
        prompt: "4.Which of these is not a peripheral, in computer terms?",
        optionA: "Keyboard",
        optionB: "Monitor",
        optionC: "Mouse",
        optionD: "Motherboard",
        answer: "Motherboard",
        number: "4",
    },
    {
        prompt: "5.Which of the following is not one of the early “protocols,” or ways to use the Internet?",
        optionA: "Blogging",
        optionB: "Telnet",
        optionC: "Gopher",
        optionD: "FTP",
        answer: "Blogging",
        number: "5",
    },
    {
        prompt: "6.What does the Internet prefix WWW stand for?",
        optionA: "Wide Width Wickets",
        optionB: "World Wide Web",
        optionC: "Worldwide Weather",
        optionD: "Western Washington World",
        answer: "World Wide Web",
        number: "6",
    },
    {
        prompt: "7.A network designed to allow communication within an organization is called:",
        optionA: "the World Wide Web",
        optionB: "Yahoo",
        optionC: "an intranet",
        optionD: "the Internet",
        answer: "an intranet",
        number: "7",
    },
    {
        prompt: "8.Which of these is not a kind of computer?",
        optionA: "Apple",
        optionB: "Lenovo",
        optionC: "Toshiba",
        optionD: "Lada",
        answer: "Lada",
        number: "8",
    },
    {
        prompt: "9.Which of these products is not made by the Apple Corporation?",
        optionA: "IMAX",
        optionB: "iPhone",
        optionC: "iMac",
        optionD: "iPod",
        answer: "IMAX",
        number: "9",
    },
    {
        prompt: "10.What is the name for a computer pointing device?",
        optionA: "A Mouse",
        optionB: "Sound Card",
        optionC: "Ram",
        optionD: "Monitor",
        answer: "A Mouse",
        number: "10",
    },
]